Hey, how's it going guys?
It is John here, and in this tutorial video,
I'm actually gonna break down a live creative
strategy process from start to finish
and show you guys exactly what I do in my agency to come up
with video ad creative strategy, how to research product,
how to research customers,
and ultimately how to research ads.
And that's really what it comes down to,
is understanding all those three pillars in order
to best come up with a creative strategy
and create a vision.
Um, whether you are scripting the ad, shooting the ad,
or editing the ad, all of those components are very critical
to coming up with the best messaging possible.
So I'm gonna be leveraging a few tools here, uh,
a few resources,
but I'm going to be, this is gonna be interesting.
I've never done this before, so I'm kind
of doing this on the fly and building as we go.
And I'll pause the video at any time if there's a,
a weird pause or I need
to create something or wait for something.
But ultimately I'm just gonna
do everything on this document.
And at the end of the video,
this document should be filled up, uh, with all
of the placeholders that you need
to inject in your next creative strategy, um, so
that you can just continue on with this and learn
and apply it for yourself.
Alright, let's get into it.
So first and foremost, I've broken it down into three steps.
And you could be selling product,
you could be selling courses,
you could be selling a service, it doesn't really matter.
Um, at the end of the day, you need
to brief yourself on the product or service.
Um, and that's, that's, that's the bare minimum, right?
So understanding the benefits
and understanding the features
of what you're actually selling.
Benefits tell, I'm sorry, benefits sell, features tell,
that's always like a easy way for me to remember.
Benefits, sell, features tell.
All right, so the next one is doing
customer avatar research.
I'm gonna be using a couple tools here that I like to
leverage in order to maximize my customer research.
And then number three, research ads.
And so that's gonna be also combined with some tools
that I, I like to use.
Um, and then pretty much from there it's gonna be
writing scripts.
All right? And we have a whole process for that,
and hopefully we can get to it in this video.
If not, I'll make it in a separate one, don't worry.
So let's get into it.
The product that we're actually gonna be
working on today is a client product that we, um,
we recently just got in from our studio,
and it is a IPL
hair removal kit.
All right, so you guys have probably heard about a product
like this before, and it, if you, if you have it,
it basically removes hair, unwanted hair with laser,
so you don't have to shave
and you don't have to, you know, spend expensive
or spend tons of money going to, uh,
expensive laser hair removal
places, and you can do it at home.
All right? So it's pretty, pretty common.
A lot of people have this product,
but the difference is right now the client wants us
to actually, he wants to market it to bald men.
Now, this is a really, really interesting angle
because I don't think it's really been done.
And so right now, yeah, he has this opportunity
to market this product to a completely new niche
and a new audience that hasn't really
discovered its potential.
So that's one thing that's really awesome about products
and marketing and angling, is that's,
that's really what the angle is.
It's like this whole time this product has been angled
and marketed towards women, women in their face,
their eyebrows, their armpits, their bikini lines,
their legs, their arms,
but no one's thought to market it to men who are balding,
who want to permanently get rid of their hair.
All right? So that's, that's
what we're gonna be talking about today,
and I'm just gonna be doing this as we go creatively
flowing, seeing where we go with it.
And so now that we're briefed on the benefits,
now let's talk about the features.
Okay, so we've got this hyper cooling, IPL technology
stops hair growth.
Uh, feature number two has a wide laser, um, allows
for quick and effective sessions, just five minute sessions.
Adjustable laser sies, nine intensely levels
digital, LED display.
Um, so this is kind of the technology behind it.
It works by selectively targeting the, the melanin
and pigment in your hair follicles.
Um, so that's what the client
provided us for the features and benefits.
If you yourself need to do a little bit further research on
the benefits and the features, I would recommend Googling it
or going to their website.
This is a brand new website, I'm sorry, brand new product.
So they don't have a direct website for it,
but you can go on Amazon, you can go to a competitor site
and find, you know, more information on it just
to get yourself really well-versed in the product.
I think this is something you can't miss,
because if you don't know how the product works,
then you're not gonna be able to sell it correctly.
And sometimes products could be really complex
and very sophisticated and difficult to use and,
or a business or like an offer just doesn't.
If you, if like, for example, me, like car insurance
or like any type of like lead gen stuff,
sometimes I don't really get it.
Um, so I have to do additional research
to really wrap my head around it.
'cause I'm so into the e-comm world.
Like, but when you, you can apply it to any niche,
obviously, you just, you need to really understand
what you're selling first.
So I'll just mark this as the what. Okay?
And next, let's move on to customer avatar.
And I'll mark this as the who.
So who are we actually looking to target?
So as you can tell, most
of this stuff is marketed towards women.
So we are gonna be marketing it towards men.
And this one's pretty easy. We're targeting men.
We're targeting men who want to,
who want a permanent way to remove hair in their heads.
Okay? So these are balding, balding men. All right?
So here's another keyword.
Balding men who want permanent hair removal,
hair removal from their heads.
Okay, so let's go back to his brief.
Um, that's pretty much all I've got for his brief,
so nothing crazy there.
Um, now I wanna do something where
I get a little bit more information.
So I'm gonna use a tool called vsl.ai.
And if you've never heard about this tool, it's a,
it's an amazing tool that allows you to generate
VSL scripts using ai.
It also allows you to do customer research using, um, ai.
I highly recommend it as a tool,
whether you're a script writer, copywriter, video editor,
um, in production.
This is, uh, this is useful
for anybody in the creative space.
And I'll walk you through it really quick
and we'll show some inputs of it and how it works
and see what we can come up with
to better understand understander audience.
Alright, so I already have a login.
Alright, so here you have your products
and I'm gonna create a brand new product.
And what it's gonna do, it's gonna prompt me right here,
product name, product description, product testimonials,
and then this is the information it needs in order
to spit out, um, all of the information
or like the customer pain points and benefits
and all those important things.
So I'm gonna go to my
creative brief and I'm going to
get the product name in here.
And excuse me if I, if I'm a little slow,
'cause we're doing this live product name is Baldy
product description.
Um, I will just start putting in
product benefits and features.
Okay? So I've got that,
I've got this,
whoops, okay.
Features, and I'm gonna see if there's anything else
that we can include in here from the client.
Um, special, Yeah,
this directions are in there.
So I'm gonna throw that in there.
Like, if you're doing this yourself, right?
You just wanna stuff as much in information in here
for the AI to use.
Usually I can go to a website and I would plug it in
and, you know, just take a bunch
of texts from there, plug it in.
But because there's no direct info, I'm just leveraging
what the customer has provided
or the, the client has provided.
So I'm gonna work with this. Next is product testimonials.
Now, I don't know if these are all gonna be valuable.
Um, we'll see, let's do head,
see if there's anything head related here.
Um, yeah, I'm just gonna,
I'm gonna throw this in there, see what happens.
All right. Okay,
so if you're, if you're t are more accurate than,
yeah, this is a crazy one.
All right, I'm gonna say that's enough for now. Okay?
I'm gonna take out these features, I don't really wanna,
all right, so I'm gonna save that.
And now I've got Baldy over here as my product,
and I'm going to create new, all right,
so this is gonna create me a customer avatar
and all of the, oops, ah, sorry, click the next step.
All right, so now it's loading
and we're just gonna wait for it to do its thing.
So this is the cool part is kind of watching it, um,
do just, its magic really.
So demographics, men
and women, generally 30 to 50 care about experience, uh,
care about their appearance
and don't wanna constantly deal with hair growth,
constant hair growth, frequent need to shave, and the pain
and discomfort associated with shaving.
All right, core sales pitch, this is very,
very important right here, right?
So this becomes like, just thinking ahead is, okay,
this is like, this is the hook, this is the the pain point,
this is the, the demonstration that we're gonna want
to focus on.
Alright? These all could potentially be, um,
angles and hooks.
So you've got emotional pain, root cause of the problem,
products promise, how it works, amazing benefits.
Yeah, all this stuff is really good.
Um, yeah, we can go really into it,
but essentially all this is stuff that we want to
copy and paste into our document.
So I'm gonna take that and I'm gonna plop it in here.
I'll go over this in just a second.
As, as I said, this is a working doc, so
we're gonna be tweaking this over time.
Um, what I tend to do is I like
to organize these further just
because it's a little easier to see.
Um, And obviously
AI doesn't provide like the perfect formatting yet,
but it gives us a little bit
of a perspective of what to do next.
So I'm applying, I'm gonna be applying different
research techniques here.
This is the vsl.ai technique, which provides me
an AI generated
research formula.
Um, but I'm just reading through this right now.
Like, what are the hesitations?
So doubts about effectiveness of home hair removal products,
biggest fear, potential pain, right?
These are, these are objections, right?
So we want to possibly include these, actually,
you probably wanna include these in the ad just
so we can, can give people peace of mind.
Uh, cultural references. Alright?
So there's no authority figure, figure story.
So I'm just going to, I'm just gonna
leave that blank for now.
Actually, some
of this background information could be used in A VSL.
So if you have like, some, some background story on
how it was made, that's where you would put
that price.
Okay? Deleting this. Okay.
All right, so we've got
all these components here
and this is just giving me a little bit more information.
And that's, that's what I'm doing. That's the whole pro.
That's the whole point of doing this product research
and strategy is like, I'm just, I'm a sponge
and I'm soaking it all in.
And let's, let's move on.
So now that I have this information, um, I'm going
to read and watch reviews.
Now, I don't know if they have any actual reviews
on this product, but I will share
that YouTube is a great place to go.
And so is TikTok.
Okay, so let's start with YouTube
and I'm gonna just jump to YouTube right now.
I'm gonna type in and I'm gonna log into a different account
because mine doesn't have ads.
So I'm gonna type in IPL
for bald, bald head.
Awesome. Here we go. Laser hair removal on your head.
Okay, let's watch. This has got 133,000 views. This is good.
Check it out. Is this the shortest haircut ever?
Right now these guys are preparing for laser hair removal
on his head, and you are thinking, who's gonna want do that?
Well, a lot of balding guys,
when they're shaving their head, they
absolutely detest the horse shoe.
Sure you can shave it every day,
but a lot of guys don't want the hassle.
The only other way, as far as I know is this,
it looks painful. What do you think?
Check out. Alright, this was a really good video. Wow. Um,
Is this the shortest,
Is this the shortest haircut ever?
There's a lot happening in this video.
And so this is, I'm gonna save this as inspiration
and I'm gonna put it into, let's put this
into a section here.
Um, I'll
just call this video inspo
and let's do YouTube at inspo
and I'll do, and to make it clean.
So there's a lot going on there.
I'll study it in just a second,
but let's go back and see what else they've got.
Here's another one's.
He's, he's, he's, He's, I don't know why it's doing,
that's all right.
So he made himself bald.
Let's see what this is all about. Head
Of hair to completely bald the hair dead
and gone, never to return.
Now, when you think of head hair,
people are usually focused on achieving a thicker,
more luscious head of hair with many undergoing surgery
and wearing aesthetic hair to achieve that fuller look.
But not Alexander,
he had spent eight years regularly shaving his head as bald
as he could possibly achieve, but it wasn't enough.
And that's when he discovered the world
of laser hair removal.
He was research high
and low in his home country of Germany for clinic.
He would do this procedure for him
after a lot of difficulty.
He found one, willing to give it a go, but
after three sessions it was a failure,
horrible experience in his own words.
This is what Alexander was left with.
Okay, this is really interesting.
Um, he's talking a lot about, you know, this patchiness,
which is like, I had no idea that this was even a thing.
Um, it sounds like he's, you know,
bald men really have an issue with this.
And this is telling me that this is like
a very emotional thing that we want to hit on.
So let's just keep watching patches
Missed. And his shoes, the laser simply
wasn't powerful enough.
It would be six years until Alexander tried again, a lot
of criticism, his parents were against it,
him achieving his follow, even forced him out
with the family home, but he wasn't her.
Six years later, some new technology arrived,
the Candela Ental pro, a machine powerful enough
for Alexander to achieve the look he desire.
Excitedly he booked his treatments, he found a place
where this machine was held and he was ready.
And here he documented his entire progress
and we can have them slough off
because now they're damage reversible from a full head
of hair to completely bald.
That's right, the hair dead and gone never to return.
Now was Alexander has actually done a fantastic job
of documenting everything to do
with this scalp hair removal.
And I think in Alexander's case, this is, I mean,
on his website here, it does say
eight two for hair fetish skies.
So, you know, maybe this is something of a specialist, uh,
desire, but more
and more we are seen guys who are getting, you know,
the rock in the horseshoe, the shaved head,
and they get fed out with shaving.
And it really does seem that this laser hair removal is the
only way to kinda counteract
that other than I guess growing out like I currently have.
So first of all, we've got the cost process range.
Alright, one second.
I think there's a, this video is teaching me a ton about,
uh, about just the bald headed community.
Um, you know, sick of shaving.
I'm sorry, I'm gonna jump around for a second just
because I don't want to uh, lose my spot,
but I'm gonna jump down to the five light bulbs over here
and get this like, as I'm taking notes
why I wanna merge this table anyways,
I'm just gonna put it down right now.
Um, they hate shaving. I heard hate shaving.
There was, um, lemme go back.
Patchy Head
Own. Alexander
was left with patch, missed any issues,
Patches missed.
Simply wasn't powerful enough.
So that's, you know, another pain point is patchy head.
They've tried laser hair removal.
And guys, if you haven't been taking the five light bulbs
training, these are different areas
that you can create better messaging for your customers.
So their status quo is, uh,
where do they wanna leave right now?
Like, what pain are they experiencing right now
that they don't want to experience?
Um, other things they've tried, other solutions,
they've tried, um, our approach, which is like
what makes us unique?
What is our offer? What are we giving them?
And then customer's, new life.
What are people saying after using the product?
It'll be six years until Alexander tried again, a lot
of criticism, his parents
were against it, him achieving his follow
Criticism. Here
we go. I'm just, I just heard criticism.
That's a big one. Um, criticism,
you know, embarrassment.
I am gonna call it like insecurity.
I'm gonna take this off just
so it's a little easier to read. Okay?
Look, even forced him out of the family
home, he wasn't deter.
Six years later some new technology arrived.
The canr gentle lay pro, a machine powerful enough
for to achieve the look he desire.
Excitedly he booked his treatments, he found a place
where this machine was held and he was ready.
And here he documented his entire progress
and we can have a swap off
because now dentist worse from a full head of hair
to completely bold.
That's right, the hair dead and gone never to return.
That was Alexander has actually done a fantastic job
of documenting everything to do
with his scalp hair removal. And I think
So he, he, he mentioned a lot of things in here right now,
I just want to go back because he just,
he just did the customer's new life right
now, powerful enough for Alexander
To, to look. He desire excitedly.
He booked his treatments,
he found a place where this machine was held and was ready.
And here he documented his entire progress
and we had them swap off
because now they're damaged from a full head
of hair to completely bald
From a full head of hair to completely bald.
Here we go. That would be customer's new life, right?
Um, com full head
to completely bald from patchy to
To bald.
All right? Other things they've tried,
I'm just speaking out loud here, obviously razors
see
Right? The hair dead and
gone never to return.
That was Alexander has actually done a fantastic job
of documenting everything to do with the scout hair removal.
And I think in Alexander's case, this is, I mean,
on his website here, it does say
it true for hair fetish guys.
So, you know, maybe this is something of a specialist, uh,
desire, but more
and more we are seeing guys who are getting, you know,
the rock in the horseshoe shaved head
and they get fed out with shaving.
And it really does seem that this laser hair removal is the
only way to kinda counteract
that other than I guess growing
out like I, uh, currently have.
So first of all, we've got the cost process range
for laser session roughly between 120 and 160 euros.
Apparently in the USA is looking about 200, 300 course.
It says if people a package, you
can get those individual sessions down.
Okay? So here is another po potential pain point.
Other things they've tried, expensive treatment, right?
This is like, I'm just gonna screenshot this 200
to $350 per single treatment.
That's huge. That's a lot of money.
Um, expensive
laser hair removal.
Um, I'm just gonna note that down as
200 to 350
per session.
That's a lot. Yeah,
this product's probably like 50 bucks maybe
To a cheaper price. And each
treatment on the head takes about 10 minutes.
So how many treatments, or apparently it may take
approximately eight to 12 treatments.
Okay? Eight to 12 treatments, that's a long time.
So eight, eight times, let's just do on the low end,
that's 1600 bucks.
All right? Um,
eight times 200, bad at math.
16 and then three 50 times eight.
So 28, so it could be up to $2,800
and that's like eight sessions. I think it's nine
After the ninth session only had some fuzzy heads growing.
He just booked the first few sessions individually.
And then you wanna do the rest of it.
You can look it as a package.
He also had that first
experience, which was a complete failure.
That situation. Does it hurt if he likens it to the feeling
of a rubber band being pulled back against the head
and snap let go, does
Snapping on, does it hurt?
Right? Um, painful,
painful process, which painful process,
Right? And then, you know,
pull, pull back
and then snap on your head.
That sounds painful,
Right?
Works best for people with light skin and dark hair.
People with light skin and dark hair, okay?
People with light skin, dark hair.
I know that with this particular product you need to have
like that contrast, otherwise it won't work as well.
Prime candidate, because the way
that this is achieved, this is kind of interesting, right?
It says only dark hair can be treated
because the laser targets the dark metal in the hair.
The laser post is nothing more than infrared radiation
that heats dark structures know
it from black tops in the
sun. So when you wear a black tshirt in the sun,
Okay, so what he's describing right now is
the, the approach.
So their approach going back here is the hypo cooling.
IPL technology stops hair regrowth at the root, right?
So we can write that down in here in our approach.
And so moving on,
Ooh, it gets hot, the hair is brightly heated,
and then the heat is released from the hair
to the adjacent blood vessels
and nutrient cells, which are destroyed
by the heat the hair dies in the best case, the hair dies
and falls out within two to three weeks.
The results are achieved with black hair on light skin,
it's dark, that absorbs the heat,
the light skin is not heated and remains intact.
Wow. But listen, I'll link his website,
I'll link his links if this is something you are
interested in.
Is this something that Dana White got?
Check out this picture here of Dana White,
right when he first machined his head.
Now if you look at today a future editing version of me,
I was gonna suggest that Dana White has had this
done based on recent pictures.
His head looks so clean, but actually
he's just got less hair than he had before.
You can see it here in this picture. So I wanna include this
because listen, if this was something you were considering,
that's also something consider as you're gonna
get older, that hair he's get less.
So I think this is another thing is they have to
call people if they want to get like a clean shave,
they have to have
to grow out their hair before shaving it.
And that will shoe, uh, if
it bothers you, it's probably gonna bother you
less. I know Alexander,
So they, they mentioned the horseshoe a lot.
I'm not sure what that is, but horseshoe,
and the reason I'm doing this is
because I'm trying to take in as much like insider,
um, verbiage, insider knowledge of the, of the,
of the customer, of the avatar
and gimme one sec.
Alright, so sorry about that.
Um, talking about the horseshoe thing.
So I'm not really sure what that is.
So I'm gonna look into that after I finish this video.
But I have a feeling it's probably an insecurity that
Is a bit of a, a special case.
Um, however he has documented this is the best documentation
I've seen on somebody getting their hair
on the head laser off.
So I wanna share with you, and for that,
I thank you Alexander, to be honest for, um,
putting this much detail about your experience.
It started off not so good, but you got there in the end,
mate, the big question is not whether the Dana Whites had
done, but would you consider this procedure?
Lemme know down in the conversation below
and Ill in the next
Video. Alright,
perfect. So I mean, this video was like spot on.
It was, it was a perfect review.
It was like a real testimonial.
And next I'm just gonna look at the comments, right?
So, oh, comment section is gold guys.
There's so much value in the comments.
All right, so we've got, I'm
Alexander, I'm the bald laser guy.
Thank you for amazing making this video.
I read a lot of the comments. I'm bl I'm a bit irritated of
how negative some guys are.
Someone seems to have a problem with something
that is 180 against the mainstream.
People should be more tolerant
and accepting decisions of others, how they look.
I just, I just hate my scalp hair since my early childhood.
Here we go. Boom. That's, that's some value right there.
Um, and I'm just gonna paste that into here.
So I have these little
snippets, okay?
I just hate my scalp. This, this right here is a hook.
I just hate my scalp hair. Since early childhood.
Boom, we found ourselves a hook
and all the time just wanted
to be smooth and bald on the head.
All right, um, here's another,
Now I'm just gonna put this, now I'm smooth
and bald on the head.
Um, I went from patchy to bald.
So another thing I'm reading is like, this is the language
that they speak to each other.
Like, I'm not bald obviously.
So I don't know what the lingo is,
but learning the lingo is, is like how you penetrate
into an a, a custom, a customer's audience
or a customer's like, um, psyche
because you're, you, you, they feel
like you understand them.
So it's partially a fetish,
but just my personal aesthetic ideal.
It's how I want to look. I'm sick of shave. Oh, here we go.
This is amazing. I'm sick of shaving
and the side effects of it and even wasting my time with it.
There we go. Here we go. That's money. That is so money.
I am sick of shaving and have, and,
and the side effects of it.
I'm easy wasting my time with it.
Um, so I started la laser treatments.
This is actually like a good,
this could be a script right here.
Um, so I started using Baldy.
Um, the most men want the most men want hair
and be afraid of getting bald.
To be perfect. Bald is a dream for me.
So please respect it and don't insult it. All right?
Most men want hair and, and get afraid of being bald.
Um, to be perfect bald is a dream for me. There it is.
I think this, this is, this is, uh, I
Something To add here too, as customer's, new life,
and I'll just rearrange this.
Most men want hair and are afraid of getting bald.
So to be perfectly bald is a dream for me. There it is.
Awesome. Let's read some, some replies.
Respect, man, I'm, I'm the same.
I accepted my hair falling after surgery 12 years ago.
Ah, here we go. I accepted my hair falling
after surgery 12 years ago, but it grows back really black
and patchy in spots.
And I'm as white as a sheet, so it's patchy and dry
and irritating and I hate shaving.
If this is readily available, I would do this in a heartbeat
and never shave again.
Woo. Look at that. That is just pure gold right there.
Good for you. Me. Alright, so I'm gonna,
I'm gonna take this comment and I'm gonna extract it.
I accepted my hair falling,
and you know what, I'm just gonna create a, a new,
I'll just put a, a new box here.
Comments, all right? Uh huh Huh.
And let's just put it up here.
Top comments and I'll put it, I'll merge this.
Okay? So
I apologize for not having this all in one place
'cause I typically have a, you know,
I do this really quickly,
but in your case, I wanna make it as clear as possible.
I'm just saying, Except in my earphone,
patchy in spots.
Okay? And I might, so it's,
it's patchy and dry and irritating and I hate shaving.
Okay, do this in a heartbeat.
Never miss shaving again. Do you hear that?
This is a huge headline right here.
Never miss shaving again. I don't need this extra.
All right, this is great. This is gonna help when
I actually start writing the script.
As you can tell. Guys, I don't know if I need
to go any further, to be honest.
Like, I feel like a lot
of my information is already here in this YouTube video.
This is teaching me so much about the customer,
how they talk, their pain points, their struggles.
This is it, man. Curious, intrusive question.
I don't see any problem with it. I am shaving up. Okay?
I don't see any problem with it. I am shaving my head every
two days and it's really time consuming since my hair is
growing like crazy.
Ooh, that's a really good line. Really powerful line.
I'm shaving my head every two days.
Uh, it's really time consuming. There we go.
Honestly, I don't really need this page.
I'm gonna close that out. I like,
I like whole process of shaving and everything,
but I would love to spend that time on something else.
There you go. If I had enough money,
I would probably go for laser.
Well, since completely accepted baldness,
since I completely accepted baldness.
Got it. I like the whole process of shaving gravers,
but I wouldn't spend that time.
Okay, so this is telling me, saving time.
All right.
If I had enough money, I would probably go for laser.
All right, check the comments. I didn't see any.
I just, you claim to have balls to be against the mainstream
is looked into this.
Deciding shaving was getting very annoying.
I shave every other day, but I would shave daily.
But I found that shaving daily irritated the skin too much
and would cause bumps.
Okay. Okay. This is good too.
All right. No hair treatment will gimme
back a level of satisfaction I get with a clean shaven head.
Decided to do price treatments, lacking remission to do it.
I decided to forget about it. I'm reinvesting.
'cause even though I shave now, you can see the halo
of stubble and it doesn't have
that streamlined shave look all around.
I'm gonna save that. Not sure what that means.
I think that's the horseshoe he's talking about.
It doesn't have that probably gonna put him on
aside for a procedure except in my bald neck.
But I, I have to shave twice a week to maintain that look.
That makes me feel comfortable the most.
So sometimes shaving feels tiresome.
I don't have the courage to go do that,
to go, There it is.
All right. Lots of common. What's the common thread here?
People, um, people don't like shaving.
I didn't realize it was such a big deal.
They're shaving very often.
Um, this is a huge angle, huge angle.
Um, people are insecure about it. I'm 27.
I've been involved since 19.
Being so young and bald made me feel like an outcast.
Ooh, there we go. Being
so young involved made me feel like an outcast.
Okay?
Um, okay.
Being so young involved made me feel like an outcast.
And the horseshoe made me look so much older than I was.
It affected my self-esteem tremendously.
So I found myself shaving very often
because I'd rather look be completely bald
than look like I'm 50.
Oh God, my heart goes out to that guy.
I didn't, I mean, I'm obviously fortunate to have hair, but,
'cause I, I don't really think too much about,
um, bald guys.
Like I don't, I think it's cool, you know, um,
but I, I imagine, you know,
it being a very big insecurity for certain people.
Uh, so I'm gonna just look up horseshoe bald.
Okay, I'm just gonna see what that looks like. Ah, okay.
So this is what the horseshoe looks like. Okay, perfect.
So this is definitely a pain point, right?
This is definitely a hook potential.
I'm just talking out loud 'cause these are just ideas.
Um, it's affected my myself.
All right, I'm gonna read a couple more comments.
The, this would be less pain temporary compared to
I'm considering making taxing my hair.
Prefer the bald look and feel of no hair.
I mean, obviously, if we're going to do this, you know,
I feel so much more confident now,
So much more confident now.
I don't, I don't feel I
my my life back.
There's a lot of benefits there.
I hate having my hair cut
and just prefer to shave it all off.
And normally do this with Phillips one blade this week.
Write it down. Okay.
For me, this whole obsession came during lockdown
with expensive haircut is I can't just, okay.
I've been shaving back when I actually had quite tried
letting it grow out a month or two.
I don't have a whole lot in the front,
so I'm never gonna do anything other than
a shave ever again.
So it would be inconvenient, but I,
I quite like the ritual of shaving every other day.
It's kind of a meditation to it.
I don't think I would ever get something like that done.
But if, you know, yeah,
I don't think lasers will permanent still come back.
Um,
okay.
Okay. So
I'm going to move this to the right hooks.
Okay. All right. So let's go back to the process.
And thanks for watching up until this point.
So we've gotten briefed on the benefits and features.
All right? We've looked up customer avatar.
We searched via cell.ai,
and this kind of helped us have a better understanding.
But after visiting YouTube, we had watched
much more in depth real people
going through this real problem.
Now, I can go to TikTok and search for stuff.
Um, this is typically if I'm doing like ad inspiration,
but YouTube is a really good place to just,
this is one thing I don't like about
TikTok is it just doesn't stop.
Um, all right.
I don't know why it's making that sound. Let's pause.
So going back to that, um, I'm gonna stick
to YouTube just for the sake of the tutorial.
I don't feel like I need to go any further.
But for, for ads, I, I will search, um, TikTok.
And if you want, you can go to reddit.com as well.
You'll find forums of people, you know, you can go to, um,
Reddit, and then
you can type in like, um, balding, I don't know,
Bald Men.
Yeah,
Bald.
There's a bunch. Here we go.
There's tons of,
uh, Tons of stuff here.
You can read the comments and check it out there.
But I feel like YouTube has
provided me a substantial amount of information.
Alright, now let's do some face, uh,
let's do some additional,
I would say concretizing, if that's a word.
I wanna summarize what I've learned just so we can begin
to look at ads.
So I hate my scalp. I've since my early childhood, okay?
I, I just feel like this is a really good hook potential.
So I'm gonna take this down here and, and put it into hook.
Before I do that, let me just explain this little,
this little box right here.
Um, this is the product.
And then like, the type of product it is,
if you've taken the training, you'll know
that I have different e-commerce types of products.
So problem solving, lifestyle, physical transformation,
life enhancing, time saving.
So these are all the potential, like I would say,
benefits, uh, to the product itself.
And it has all these potentials like physical
transformation, it's life enhancing tech.
There's a time saving aspect to it.
Um, so that's going to kind of affect how the,
the videos are scripted.
Um, so I can probably expand further on the avatar
and audience now that I know more.
So it's balding men
who want permanent hair removal from their heads
and don't want to, um, waste
more time, um, shaving their head
and want to feel confident
with a perfectly bald head.
Okay. Um,
for this particular, yeah, I mean,
we could probably refine that further.
Um, all right, so balding men
who want permanent hair removal from their heads.
I mean, that's kind of redundant.
Uh, and don't wanna waste more time shaving their
heads, shaming their heads with razors,
um, and want a perfectly confident bald head
at an affordable price.
Okay? 'cause price, I think is a big one there too.
So I'm gonna summarize that really quick again.
So balding men, just in bullet points.
Um, permanent hair removal,
no more shaving.
Um, feel confident, feel,
look, yeah, obviously look more attractive,
feel more confident and don't, don't waste
and, and save money on laser treatments, right?
So I feel like this is a good representation
of what we just studied.
And, excuse me, I got my, my toddler here. He's pee pee.
He's going in one sec. All right, we're back.
Sorry, my kid, how to use the restroom.
All right, so let's go back. I feel like this kind
of summarizes balding man.
Permanent hair removal, no more shaving looks more
attractive, feel confident.
Save money on laser treatments.
Like this is copy for the website, right?
This is copy for image ads.
This is copy for anything at this point now
that we're really narrowing down who we're talking to.
Um, so I'm just gonna read through these comments again.
I'm sick of shaving and the side effects of it. This is it.
This is another hook. I wanna keep it nice and simple.
Um, and I'm going to bring it down here to this hook section
just as a way for me to remember.
Okay? Um, I would say shot of horseshoe
head horse.
Did I spell that wrong? Shot
of patchy Achi.
Okay, let's call this, I'm just gonna add, uh,
headline hooks and then to the right,
I'm gonna add visual hooks.
Okay? As I was going through this,
I was learning more about it.
Um, shot of patchy head
versus clean head, or it could just be patchy head there.
This could probably be, those,
could be two individual ones, patchy head.
Okay. Uh, what else?
So I think there's another one of, um,
shot, there's a picture that I found of that guy, right?
Like this one where he is like growing it out.
Um, so like a shot of man
trying to grow out his hair to shave.
Uh, that's that patchy spots.
And why is it she, it's itchy and dry. Irritating. Okay.
I hate shaving. My head is always patchy
and dry after shaving.
So that's, that could be another,
let's try that as a headline.
Hook my head.
My scalp. My scalp is always
so patchy and dry.
Patchy. I would probably keep it to like, patchy
and irritating or dry
and irritating and irritated.
Okay. Um,
I'm never going back to shaving again.
That could be another headline.
Okay? I'm shaving my head every two days.
It's really time consuming since my
hair is growing like crazy.
Um, I think,
and when it just came up, I wish I found this
Scalp,
scalp remover.
I don't know if you wanna call it a scalp remover.
Um,
scalp remover.
Okay. Get close ups of ingrown here and raise your burn.
That's another demo
for bald men sooner.
Show razor burn
and bumps on head.
Okay? All right.
Lemme see if I can just make this a little prettier for you.
I am unsure where the,
all right, we are back.
We are just going through the rest of these.
Shaving was getting really annoying.
Found that Dave irritated the skin cause bumps.
Okay, so we got that shaving every day is so annoying.
Shaving every day is so annoying.
Okay, shaving my head,
my scalp every day.
Shaving money is getting annoying.
Halo of stubble twice a week.
Being young, being so young
involved makes me feel like an outcast.
This is a good one. It's a very like, insecurity point.
You could also be a a, a line in the, in the video too.
Okay? I'd rather be completely bald than
look like I'm 50 there.
That's a good one too. Whew. Good hooks.
All right, perfect.
All right, so where are we at in the process?
We are researching ads.
We finished step two, now we're gonna research some ads,
find some ad inspiration.
Um, so I like to use Facebook ad library.
I'll link that in just a second.
And I don't know if we're gonna find very many ads for this,
because there's a very, like, rare angle.
Um, but we can look at YouTube.
Um, let's go, let's go back
and we can see some shorts here.
Oh, here we go.
Alright, We're gonna play yes
or no on this scout care routine.
According to a dermatologist,
he's got some scarring on the back of the scalp,
so this is gonna be difficult to treat.
Ooh, uh, we're putting lemon on there.
This is a no no for me.
Now we're following that up with baking soda.
That's all. That's also a no.
Oh my God, I, I can't even watch that. Morning. Morning.
Alright, we're gonna, We're gonna, we're, we're, we're,
we're gonna, we're gonna, we're gonna, we're gonna, we,
We, all right. So I
really feel like this ad, let's go back to this ad
because this one, it's not even an ad,
but I feel like it's really good shortest
Haircut ever. Right
now these guys are preparing,
All right, is this the shortest haircut ever, right?
This is a really good hook. Um, let's go down.
This is the shortest haircut ever.
Let's just watch the rest of this again,
The laser hair removal on his head.
And you are thinking, who's gonna wanna do that?
Well, a lot of balding guys,
when they're shaving their head, they
absolutely detest the horse shoe.
The horse shoe, that's the big one. Sure,
You can shave it every day,
but a lot of guys don't want the hassle.
The only other way, as far as I know,
is this, it looks painful. What do you think?
Nice. All right, check it
Out. Is this the,
The, here's what we can do.
We'll go to TikTok and we'll type in, uh,
laser hair removal for your head.
Okay? 'cause there's actually not that much going on.
Oh, here we go.
Hey guys, my name is Andrew,
and this is my first YouTube video.
And what I want to talk to you guys about is male
baldness and laser hair removal.
Now, I know those two terms sound really scary together,
but I, obviously we don't have to be.
And I hope that this video and the future
videos I'm gonna make, show you guys that.
So, to tell you a little bit about myself, I'm 28 years old.
When I was 21, I started losing my hair pretty
ably, and I did what a lot of guys do.
I started to get really tight fades,
and I started wearing hair out really long on top.
And for a few years, it, it did hide it.
You couldn't really tell that I was losing my hair that bad
until I was about 25, and then I could really notice nothing
I did behind it.
And my self-confidence took a pretty big blow.
I took a lot of pride in my hair looked like,
and it was a big part of my self image.
And I just didn't know what to do about being 25
years old and losing my hair.
So, about a year ago when I was
27, I decided, you wanna know what?
I'm tired of it. I don't like consistent. Look,
I'm gonna just, um, cut my hair really short.
So I did is I clip it down to nothing with zero guard.
And I did that for a while. But you could still tell in
really bright conditions if it was really sunny outside
or if the lighting was really bright, you could still tell
that I was losing my hair with a zero guard.
And so about six months ago, I decided, you wanna know what?
I'm gonna own it. I'm gonna be bald.
I'm gonna shave my head every day with razor.
I'm got a consistent look finally,
and I'm just gonna own it.
I'm gonna get rid of this hair, it's gonna be my ass.
And I loved it and I still love it.
And everybody who sees it and sees why I used to, like,
they all like to change the change that I had.
But what I didn't realize is that
shaving your head every single day is a big task.
Even if you get really good at it
and you get super quick with it, the
least amount of time it takes for me is five minutes.
And there's nothing I can do to shorten that time.
I just didn't wanna spend the rest of my life
shaking my head every single day.
And so I decided to look into whether
or not I could get laser hair removal on my head.
And there are a few guys on YouTube who cover this topic,
and there's a few, um, articles
online about it, but there is a whole lot.
And so I wanted to add to it, I wanna show you guys
what the process is of laser hair removal For this video.
And other days I've had two treatments so far,
and I'm about two weeks out for my second treatment.
So my laser hair removal specialist will let me
come every four weeks for treatment.
So this is two weeks.
Keep in mind, this is two weeks after my second treatment.
So to take up the first treatment,
All right? So he's confirming
everything
that we've already researched about the time, you know,
inconvenience aspect of things, which is really good.
So this makes sense. Um, I didn't really notice anything
and I thought, oh no, I pay all this money.
And nothing really happened until about
two weeks after the first treatment.
And I started to see patches, even my shoulder
Daddy, I could see patches.
And I said, wow, this is great.
And then I started coming out even morning.
I got really, really patchy. So I went
get the second treatment.
Um, I assumed I would have a similar outcome, and I did.
So now I'm two weeks out from the second treatment
and my hair is really, really patchy.
So I'm going to then I head over a little
bit, show you guys, and I'm gonna kinda turn around.
I want you guys to see, but looks like,
keep in mind the lighting isn't perfect in this room
and the back of my head in person,
you can tell it's starting to get kinda patchy,
but the video doesn't show me that
while I've already tried it.
But just keep in mind, um, it's really noticeable
in the video and person on the sides on top.
It's not so noticeable on the back, at least on this video.
So this is what the top of my head looks like.
And then if I go to the side,
this is what the, my left side looks like.
You can tell it's getting really, really thin
around my here and up here.
And if I come around to this side, you can tell,
especially right here, there's a, there's a line.
I think she behind this. You can tell again, really thin.
And then if I turn all around,
hopefully you guys can see this, the camera,
but you can kind of tell it's not.
The results are notice swollen in the back.
Um, like I said, I this my first time, forgive me,
but it's not as noticeable in the back.
Um, like I said on camera, we can't see it in person.
And I hope that gives you guys a good idea
of what this process looks like.
Um, about being a quarter of the way through.
So I'm gonna have this video in the future.
What I wanna do is I'm gonna take a video right
before I get to treatment about halfway between treatments.
Um, and I'm gonna just keep making videos until it's done.
So my goal for this at the very
end is to be completely balded.
I don't wanna have to take a razor in my head anymore.
I'm tired of that. Um, I wanna be just
completely bald on the top of my head.
So if you like this video, please
like it. Please comment on it.
All right. So he kinda said the same stuff
that we've already known and that's fine,
but it just reaffirms what we, uh, God,
these videos are terrible.
Um, reaffirms what we already know.
So from here, yeah, let's look at ad types.
Let's see if there's any ads out there.
I'm gonna go to, uh, Facebook ad library.
Lemme just link this here. It's already there.
And I'm gonna type in, um, I'm just gonna type in bald head.
We have those ones. We have those
Guys type in balding. Actually, you
Have to disguise.
Mm-Hmm.
Oops.
Here we go. You're gonna see, let's see.
A lot of hair loss ads. All right.
This is the natural solution to hair loss.
Helps promote your hair's. Look, thickness and growth.
It's not just about the great products,
it's about the mission of helping
To create a blueprint of poverty alleviation.
This is actually pretty good. So I wanna save it to my ads
Four times a week Like that.
I like the formatting of this, how my
Hair went from this to this.
Ooh, try is try award-winning black castor oil from Creole
essence to reduce breakage
and promote fuller, healthier hair.
Loved by over 50,000 customers
and seen in people Forbes and Marie Claire.
It is a hundred percent natural and very ethical.
This oil is known to promote the growth
and thickening of hair, eyebrows,
and eyelashes while soothing muscle aches
and fading stretch marks
100% pure Haitian castor seed oil.
It's a good ad. It's a really good ad.
I think I like the script. I'm gonna save that to my ads.
And by the way, I'm using magic brief
to save this to my ads.
I'll show you that in just a second.
Ooh, I really like this thumbnail. This is crazy.
My hair grew like crazy.
Once I threw this out of my kitchen,
I threw away all my cooking oils to fix my balding hair.
Here's why. Black women with thing,
hair receding edges and bald spots,
Severe SL Is there something in my diet
that causes my hair loss?
The answer is yes. And I have learned this the hard way.
Turns out I had this one ingredient in my kitchen
that I have used religiously almost every day.
That makes your bald spots bigger, your edges even thinner,
and your overall hair loss even worse
because it accelerates the underlying cause
of black women's hair loss.
A sneaky scalp condition which eats
through your hair follicles and
Causes. It's a good, good.
This is very good editing. Good
Scription was and how to stop it.
My hair went from this to this in just 40 days.
Keep watching because I am going to show nothing.
All this is great, but it's not a hundred percent related
to what we're doing 'cause it's the opposite.
Um, but I just want to get some frameworks in place.
All right. There's like a transformation video
there. Here we go.
Tired of dealing with baldness or hair loss.
Introducing scalp, micro-pigmentation.
Here we go. smp,
This is the most popular solution to hair loss.
It's risk-free and lasts long term.
It recreates a close shaven style using a
natural pigment ink.
Three sessions are needed for a realistic look.
Here we go. Serve Your free consultation today
and get the best price for your new hair.
It's not bad. That's a good ad. That's a good ad.
I like these voiceovers.
Trying to stop thinning hair. Avoid these common mistakes.
The best way to stop hair loss is not with finasteride.
It's not with minoxidil.
And my God, I can promise
you it's not with hair supplements.
Actually, did you know the last FDA approved hair loss
solution was all the way back in 1992.
And just to put things into perspective, that was 10 years
before the first ever iPhone and 20 years
before Instagram even came out.
Can you imagine how much has changed since then?
But that's exactly the same old
and outdated technology we're still using
in the hair loss industry today.
But it begs the question, how the f**k is that possible?
I've been obsessed with finding answer to that question
for the last 22 years.
When I started battling hair loss myself,
I went from literally being voted best hair in high school
to a severely receiving hairline
and balding around the crown.
And to say that hair loss affected me emotionally
and my mental health will be a
dramatic understatement today.
Thank God my hair is better than ever,
but I can tell you it is not from
what every big hair loss brand
is telling you is the best solution.
In fact, look at these results.
Even most hair loss experts don't believe
results like these are possible.
And no, not one of these.
Sorry, I thought of another idea.
Just I wanted to write it down.
And shaving for good
and scalp shaving.
Forget. So I mean, these are typical people.
These are, these are our audience members as well.
But these are people looking for, you know, hair growth,
Trying to stop thinning hair, avoid these common,
Um, so I like, I like that video.
He is very straightforward about it.
This is not real. Oh, this,
this is a little too much for me.
I don't wanna watch that. All right.
Trying to stop. Same ad
Finding a permanent solution to hair loss.
Introducing scalp micro-pigmentation. That was
Just a different hook.
Hair loss made me lose all my confidence,
but luckily my man gave me this.
It's a high frequency wand
that uses frequency electrotherapy, which when used on the
scalps improves blood circulation resulting in
strengthening hair follicles.
I use it three times a week for 15 minutes.
And I notice baby hairs on my balding areas.
I now comes with 50% off and free attachments for your skin.
It's a high selling product,
so they're selling out quickly. Hair loss.
All right, I like this video because it's just
singular talking or like
demonstration plus voiceover. Here's how
I started balding in my thirties,
those tight braids and weaves.
Girl, they did a number on my hair, left me
with thinning patches that had me tweeting under hats.
Then I found my hair savior. Yes, melanin.
It's a hair regrowth system made just for us black women.
The secret sauce, African chubby powder.
This stuff is like finding gold.
Rarely seen in other hair products,
but it's a total game changer for black women's hair.
This little gem protects our precious hair follicles from
the havoc wreaked by those tight hairstyles.
We love give yes melanin
Good ad too, man.
Where was writing these for African
American women are just crushing it. I love it.
Here's how I, here's how I start.
Here's how I start, here's how I start.
Same hook. Um, all right,
Tired of dealing with baldness or hair loss.
Introducing scalp, micro-pigmentation or
SMP. So I can tell
they're testing hooks. That's good.
SP is a treatment using pigments
and specially designed direct control. Very similar.
Yeah, all of these ads that I just saved
can be transformed and converted into this new ad,
or I'm sorry, into this ad creative.
So what I'm looking for is the script structure
and the ad style, and I'm going to model that
and then create my scripts on top of it.
So let's go to the process again
and looks like we've got some Now I got some videos saved.
Um, I'll throw in TikTok in there.
And to be honest, I feel like I have enough to play with.
But let's see if we got IPL
Hair loss or hair removal.
Oh, scalp.
Let's see if scalp. Oops, I spelled that wrong.
Let's see.
Oh man, I just bought one
of these home IPL devices designed
for laser hair removal use at home.
And I'm gonna compare that to the IPL device
that I have in my office, which is great.
At hair remover, I've drawn a line down my neck,
so we can do a split neck comparison
between these two devices.
We're using the home one first on the left side of my neck,
And it looks very familiar At all.
We were able to go through my neck,
and it's not a real fast device.
Individual pulses designed
to target the pigment at the hair follicle.
It's gonna take several sessions
before you see results from hair removal,
but I have a feeling because this one didn't hurt very much
at all, I'm not gonna get a lot of results from it.
I'm gonna compare that to IPL with my device
and we use gel on the skin to conduct the light
and this treatment goes much faster.
Wow. And you could really feel the difference.
It was more uncomfortable, but the pain goes away
fast after the treatment.
Barely any redness on the left, lots of redness on the
Right. Interesting. Follow
Along to see results after several weeks.
Interesting. All right,
so it doesn't really look like there's a lot of, um,
scalp for IPL on on TikTok right
now, which is fine.
Um, but there's a lot of, yeah,
there's a lot of videos on IPL in general,
so I'm pretty happy with the stuff that I have.
I think we have our angles in place and the video types.
So next thing I'm gonna do is, um,
I'm gonna log into my magic brief
and I will put a link into Magic Brief into this document.
But let's go into magic Brief
and let's create ourselves a new collection.
We'll call this Baldy, create a Collection. All right?
And let's go to my ads.
And I'm just gonna go to add details
and search Baldy,
and then I'm gonna just save these recent ones
into my collection.
Why am I doing this? So I can easily
review them and compare.
Basically, I'm going to break down the different styles
of each one so I can recreate them.
All right? I'm gonna look at a couple IIPL videos.
Okay, so this one 7.2 million, 5.4 million.
These are, these are heavy hitters right here.
I'm gonna save this and then I'm gonna save that as well.
Anything over a million, I'm typically saving on TikTok.
Oh, there's a good one. A million.
There's A lot of good ones here.
Did you know 7.6 million? Wow.
All right, let's check this out.
So let's go back to our, where'd it go?
Match brief. We're gonna go to my ads
and I'm gonna save these guys.
Baldy.
All right, Baldy.
All right, so that one's already safe.
What's great about Magic Brief is
that it does provide the script for you,
and this is something that's super valuable if you go
to the AI frames here, okay?
And click on that.
It will provide you with the screenshots, the frames,
and with the, uh, the script itself.
This is awesome because then I can go
to copy script right here and then start creating my script.
Um, so with that, now let's start writing our scripts.
So when writing our scripts, we want to determine,
you know, we want to determine the, the video A style,
and we want to basically
create, I mean like, if, if we're going to
do it the magic brief way where we copy the script, um,
copy script from magic Brief,
and then from here, I think it's really important to label,
Label your scenes,
and we'll go over what that means in just a second.
And then you want to actually rewrite your script,
uh, add your B roll,
add your hooks, okay?
This is the, this is the whole process.
So let's just get straight into it.
I am gonna go over to our shot list
and actually move over here just
because it's a little bit easier for me to work with.
But in this video that I share with you guys,
I'm gonna organize it, make it look real nice for you,
and then share it with you as a template
so it's easy for you guys to follow.
But I'm gonna move over to here
and just work on this video.
So, uh, for this particular package,
we're actually offering three different, I'm sorry, um,
six different UGCs.
So this is UGC number one,
and we're offering two different actors.
So each one will have a different look and feel.
But here's how I'm gonna do that.
Let's go back to magic brief.
All right, so let's just say that this is one, um,
particular style,
and I'm just gonna copy this script right here.
And I'm gonna go to my actual script,
and I'm gonna paste that here.
All right, so it's gonna give it
to you in this weird format.
Um, but I'm gonna just
put them into their columns like this.
So I'm gonna pause it and get back to you.
All right, so I put the script now into the
voiceover column.
Now this is optional. Um, what I like to do if I'm like
modeling after a script is I'll add an extra column just
as a, let's say reference, and then I'll delete it later.
But sequence, um, this is your hook. Introducing.
So I'll do intro S and p. What is it?
Um, how it works, how it works.
Uh, this is benefits.
Benefits. Uh, take control of your hair,
give yourself a next level tattoo.
Basically, you want to, yeah, customer's, new life,
um, benefits, CTA.
So a lot of benefits in this video. All right.
Um, so now I can just rewrite this. Now, there's a few ways.
I mean, I could use chat GPT to rewrite this if I wanted to.
Um, I could, we could try it. I don't mind trying it.
So let's go to chat GPT right now.
And what I'm gonna do is I'm gonna put all these parameters
that we, we got from
VSL ai, and I'm gonna plug them into chat.
GPT. Um, I am looking
for a UGC script for, I just like
to talk to Chad, GBT just because I, it's my friend.
Uh, amazing. Uh,
here are the product details.
Okay? Boom.
And then I need the script
following this format.
All right, so I'm gonna go back to my script here
and I'm gonna break down these little things
and I'm gonna tell chat, this is the format that I want.
Um, keep it, um, under,
I think, how long was this ad?
Like, let's go back
and look at it really quick.
Under 30 seconds. Let's keep it under 30 seconds.
Let's 30 seconds. All right, let's see what happens.
Okay, tireless hair growth. Discover the hair removal.
Meet Baldy.
All right. Okay. It's almost there.
Yeah, I think we're almost there.
Yeah, this is pretty solid.
So, um,
rewrite it strictly for this avatar.
Okay, I am gonna go back to my strategy
and
give it a little bit more information.
I will do customer pain points. Um,
these are a little bit more recent
or like Customer.
All right, let's see what happens.
Okay, balding man, tired
of constantly shaving, patchy hair growth.
Introducing Baldy, the ultimate hair removal technology
designed for men who prefer a sleek,
completely bald look without the hassle
with baldy hyper cooling IPL technology achieve permanent
or permanent hair removal, say goodbye
to irritating time shaving routines.
Imagine never having to do with razor bumps
or the halo of stubble.
Again, Baldy makes it a reality brace.
A younger, more confident you Baldy helps you maintain
that clean, attractive look.
Okay, this is good. This is great. I don't
Want, All right, I'm gonna talk
to GPT and tell it.
This is great. Let's, uh, reduce the amount
of words and keep it really simple
under 30 seconds.
Okay,
there we go.
Balding man. Ready to ditch the razor for good meat.
Baldy permanent solution to, there we go.
Effortless, painful. No more shaving. No more patchy growth.
Look younger. Feel confident. This is fantastic.
There it is. That's our script, guys. We nailed it.
All right, let's take this over here.
And I'm gonna delete this 'cause we don't need that anymore.
And I'm gonna delete that.
Actually put, paste that in here.
All right,
savings.
Okay, so it kind of rewrote this stuff, which is cool.
It's fine. So you can tell there's no like perfect system
right now for this kind of stuff,
but this is what works for me right now.
All right, benefit.
I mean, I could probably add more
benefits to this to be honest.
Let's see if we can add two more benefits.
This is a good hook.
What does this say?
Savings. All right,
I'm gonna delete this column.
Okay, can you add,
can you add a social proof section?
And one more benefit,
This is good too.
Balding joined the Baldy revolution,
scape from daily shaving
benefit to, here we go.
So where are we at? Effort. Effortless.
No more patchy shaving. No more patchy growth.
Look, feel younger. Say goodbye to daily shaving hassles.
Um, thousands of men.
There we go.
Let's go. Sh proof here.
Thousands of men are already, just
check out our glowing reviews.
Yeah, I think that's solid, man. That's a good script.
So this is gonna be, I'm gonna call this like
voiceover plus B-roll style.
All right? And that's gonna be that.
So, and obviously I can fill out the
shot description here,
but I mean it's pretty self-explanatory for now.
Um, but I'll do it.
For example, balding man, show balding man
shaving his head.
Um, show baldy in use.
Um, show before and after after this. Painless balls.
No more shaving show,
painful shaving.
Show patchy growth.
Look younger, feel confident, say goodbye.
Show super confident bald man.
Show razors being thrown away
or show painful process.
Save time and money. NOCO treatments.
Um, show how expensive laser
treatments are.
Um, show product
in use thousands of men.
Okay? Show social proof star
ratings plus other UGCs.
Join the Baldy revolution.
Be bold, be bold, be confident, get yours.
Now I would say, you know, show before
and after plus product in use plus end screen.
Okay, fantastic. There it is.
So that's the whole scripting process right there.
Um, I mean, we can try to do this one more time
and then that's gonna be it, but let's give it a go.
So what I'd like to do is I'll just
duplicate this one more time.
I'll call this VUGC number two,
and let's see what we got for examples
that we can pull from.
Um, let's watch these. These are really long.
Wow, two minutes. Pull my
Life. I want it to look
like a hairless cap. Okay, no hair for,
Okay, I'm not gonna wash this two minutes. I've been
Using the Phillips Lumia for six weeks now.
Here are my results. This is before using it.
This is for day's hair growth.
This is for day's growth after the first two weeks
after for weeks still growing, but it's slowing down.
This is after six weeks.
I am so pleased with the results so far.
All right, so this one shows like a transformation.
I don't know if we're gonna be able to do
that with the product. Why
Am I nervous?
Oh, this is good. Oh,
I'm gonna turn this all the way up to level
five, the highest level.
Now I'm nervous. Okay,
that actually does not hurt at all.
Well, Just a reaction, live reaction.
It's not bad. Go well,
I guess on Thursday.
All right, that's cool.
Um, oh yeah,
this is the ad that I wanted to copy. Yeah, it almost
Made me lose all my confidence, but luckily
My, yeah, this is the one that I want to copy.
All right, let's look at the frames. Copy script.
Let's go down here. Let's delete all this.
Oops. Okay. All right.
Hair loss, maybe lose,
but luckily gave me this.
All right, I'll pause. All right, so I went through
and I basically added little sequences here to my video,
and I'm going to go into chat, GPT
and say thank you.
I need a new script
following this format.
Okay.
Oops. And
please rewrite it to the
recent benefits and features.
Okay, I'm just gonna make this look a little nicer for chat.
I don't know if it makes a difference,
but I'm gonna do it anyways.
All right, let's see what happens.
I lost shatter my confidence,
but then his life changer, it's not just a wand,
um, it's frequency.
My made name.
Sorry, let's rewrite this for Baldy.
Um,
can I spell it right?
Certainly right about that.
Alright, let's see. This thing, thing going.
Battling hair loss really hits my confidence hard,
but then I found Baldy and everything changed.
Baldy isn't any just hair.
It's breakthrough in scalp care using da da da.
This is great. It's a great add.
This means a per permanent smooth bald look without the
constant hassle of shaving.
Just a few treatments, eight to 12 weeks
and changes a remarkable nor packed spots.
Oh, this is amazing. Perfect.
Okay, this ad is fantastic. Just give you a thumbs up there.
Good job. Alright, let's go
and put this into our script template.
All right, and I'll be right back.
All right, I put it back in this shot list format.
Now battling with hair loss really hit my confidence hard.
Just go back to here and find some, um, here we go.
Shot of horseshoe head.
All right, so I'm gonna show shot of horseshoe head.
This could just be an image to be honest.
Um, then I found Baldy Show, um,
person holding Baldy
and about to use it.
Um, show person using it on scalp
show closeup on scalp with product
and use this means a permanent smooth look without constant
hassle of shaving show, um,
Hassles of shaving poop.
Okay. All right, sorry about that.
Um, this means permanent show hassle of shaving.
Then show clear
before actually just show hassles of shaving
show clear before and
after show model, um,
showing off his smooth head.
Okay, right now, show product
plus in use show
confident man.
All right, there it is guys.
That is another B roll plus vo.
So guys, that's the entire tutorial.
Um, pretty much from here we would just fill out little
details of props, prep and get it ready for shooting.
Um, and there it is my whole process from ideation,
from research to ideation to scripting
all in one go.
And we made good time here.
So I'm gonna go ahead
and organize this document for you so it's nice
and clear and easy to follow.
And hopefully you guys can start doing this
yourself and I'm excited.
So shoot me a message if you have any questions
and I hope you enjoyed this training.
Cheers.